rctoys.com 2010-11-22

# Privacy Policy - Draganfly Innovations Inc. : RCToys.com

**Draganfly Innovations Privacy Commitment to Our Customers**  
We at Draganfly Innovations value our customers and respect their privacy. We only collect as little customer information as needed in an effort to provide you with a great shopping experience. We will only communicate with you about our products, services, new products, sales and promotions via email if you have signed up for a newsletter or forum. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. 

If you have any questions about our policies you can always contact Draganfly Innovations customer service department in any of the following methods: 

  * Email: [sales@rctoys.com](http://www.rctoys.com/support/index.php?x=&mod_id=4&t=1)
  * Phone: 1-800-979-9794 or 306-955-9907
  * Fax: 306-955-9906
  * Write to: Draganfly Innovations Inc 2108 St. George Avenue Saskatoon, Saskatchewan S7M 0K7 Canada

We may change or amend our policies at anytime. These changes will be posted on the Web site and a revision date will appear at the end of this document. 

**Quick links within this page:**

  * [How do I access my information? How do I change or delete my information?](http://www.rctoys.com/draganfly-innovations-information/PRIVACY-POLICY.html#account_info)
  * [How do I exercise my preferences about receiving promotional communications via mail or email?](http://www.rctoys.com/draganfly-innovations-information/PRIVACY-POLICY.html#account_promos)
  * [Regarding orders valued greater than $2,000.00 and shipping to the USA](http://www.rctoys.com/draganfly-innovations-information/PRIVACY-POLICY.html#us_customs)

##   
What kind of information does rctoys.com collect?

We collect information, such as name, postal addresses, email, phone number from you when you place an order online, by phone, save your info with us online, and if you sign up for a newsletter. If you ordered with a credit card we collect that info as well. If you created an account on our online store your credit card number is not stored with your account. We do maintain records of your purchases that you have made online or by phone. This is so you can see your order history and track your orders.

##   
How does rctoys.com use my information?

When you place an order or make a purchase from rctoys.com, we only use your personal information to process your order, send you e-mails to confirm your order or to contact you via phone, postal mail or e-mail if we have other questions regarding your order or purchase with us. Since we also provide technical support on many of our products, we may inform you if there is an upgrade or recall on a product. This will also be posted on our main website. Draganfly Innovations will not send you promotional information, surveys or announcements via email or mail unless you have signed up for one of our newsletters or forums. You may opt out of these mailings at anytime.

##   
How do I access my information? How do I change or delete my information?

You can always access you information by logging into your account you created on our Web site. Once logged in you can alter any of this information (ex: address, email, phone number etc). If you are having difficulty, please contact us via email or call us and we can assist you with these changes. Remember that Draganfly Innovations does not require you to create an account to place an order with us! If you want to delete your account please call us.

##   
How do I exercise my preferences about receiving promotional communications via mail or email?

Draganfly Innovations will only send you promotional information if you have signed up to a newsletter or forum. If at any time you decide you do not wish to be a part of the mailing, please click here to instantly unsubscribe. You can also [email](mailto:info@rctoys.com?Subject=Unsubscribe%20me%20from%20your%20email%20mailling%20list), call, write to us or fax us. We will remove you from the list. This may take up to 10 business days to complete. Draganfly Innovations will not send you promotional information, surveys or announcements via email or mail unless you have signed up for one of our newsletters or forums. You may opt out of these mailings at anytime.

##   
Regarding orders valued greater than $2,000.00 and shipping to the USA

United States Border Services requires that all items shipping from Canada to the United States that are valued greater than $2,000.00 USD must show the TAX ID or Social Security Number for the Importer of Record. This is mandatory and must be on the Commercial Invoice and the Worldwide Services Waybill.

When shipping to US Businesses, the business TAX ID is required, and when shipping to individuals, the SSN is required. For additional information regarding new procedures that were in effect as of October 1st, 2004, please visit the U.S. Border Services Agency Web site [www.customs.gov](http://www.customs.gov/). You may also download the [Official Customs Directive](http://www.rctoys.com/pdf/Official-Customs-Directive.pdf).

Please rest assured that we will only use your number for the shipping documents and we do not keep it on file. If you need clarification or have any questions, please do not hesitate to contact us by email at [info@rctoys.com](mailto:info@rctoys.com) or by telephone toll-free at 1-800-979-9794 (306-955-9907 outside of North America).

##   
How does rctoys.com protect kids' privacy?

Draganfly Innovations is concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet and will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. We are also a member of the BBB Kids Online Reliability Program. With all computer use, parents should ensure they are supervising their children while on the internet.

##   
Credit Card Safeguard

At rctoys.com we always do our best to provide a safe and seamless online shopping experience. We always safeguard the integrity of our customers' credit card information. If you believe your credit card/debit card has been used in an unauthorized manner on our site (as determined by your credit card company), we will work together with the credit card company to provide any information we can to their fraud department.

We also accept PayPal as a form of payment that many online customers feel safer using. If this is still not enough to make you comfortable, you can always place your order via phone with one of our customer service reps at 1-800-979-9794 or International customers at 1-306-955-9907. We can provide many options to satisfy your concerns.

##   
Credit Card Safety

Protecting the safety of your credit card information is very important to us so we At Draganfly Innovations utilize SSL (Secured Sockets Layer) technology, which uses advanced encryption methods to ensure that the information you send us is secure. We ensure that your transaction is safe and hassle free.

##   
CVV (credit card security code)

Draganfly Innovations does require that you to enter your credit card's 3 to 4 digit security code (CVV). This information is on the actual credit card and we feel makes the transaction more secure. We cannot process your order online or via phone without it. If there is ever a concern regarding the card, we do call for authorization to the card issuing bank as an extra step for our customers' security as well as ours. If you have any questions about this requirement, please contact us.

##   
Bank or credit card company liability

Under the Fair Credit Billing Act (US customers only) your card issuing bank or credit card company cannot hold you liable for more than $50 of unauthorized or fraudulent charges on a credit card. The liability for any unauthorized use of a debit card may be higher or different, so always check your cardholder agreement with your bank. Remember: If unauthorized use of your credit or debit card does occur, you must notify your card provider, in accordance with the agreement you have with the company.

##   
Your credit card information is secure

To ensure you are accessing our secure server when you are about to submit your personal financial information, look on your Web browser for a Closed Lock icon in one of it's toolbars. If you see the closed lock then SSL is active. To double-check for security on the site, please look at the URL, Location or Address bar in your Web browser. On the secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should read "https://" not just "http://" (the S means it is secure). 

##   
Web Browsers

To use our Web site you need to be using one of these supported Web browsers: FireFox 1.5+, Netscape 7+, Internet Explorer 6.0+, Opera 10+, Safari 1+. All these Web browsers are free to download from their Web sites.

Unsupported Web browsers are Netscape 2, 3, 4 and 6, Internet Explorer 3, 4 and 5. Mac users please note: Internet Explorer for Mac is not supported. Please use Safari, Netscape 7+, FireFox, or Opera 10+.

##   
Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that is stored on your computer's hard drive when you visit a Web site. A cookie may contain information such as logged in/out status, your shopping cart contents, etc. Cookies are required to ensure that you have a good online shopping experience with us. We do not store personally identifiable information or credit card information in your cookie. By default Cookies should be enabled on your Web browser. If you turn off cookies you will not be able to shop online from our site. If you need to enable cookies in your Web browser do a [Google search](http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&lr=&q=how+to+enable+cookies+web+browser) for Web sites that tell you how. 

##   
Javascript

Javascript needs to be enabled in your Web browser to use our Web site. Your Web browser should have Javascript enabled by default. Javascript and Java are two completely different languages, even though they sound similar. You do not need Java to use our Web site. If your firewall does not allow Javascript from the Internet in general, you will need to ask your network administrator to enable Javascript for the rctoys.com If you need to enable Javascript in your Web browser do a [Google search](http://www.google.com/search?q=how+to+enable+javascript+web+browser) for Web sites that tell you how. 

Document, Audio & Video Plug-Ins

A few plug-ins may enhance your shopping and product research experience at rctoys.com To view our videos, experience multimedia effects, and view charts and statistics forms on products, and take advantage of other features, you need to download and install the following free plug-ins. 

* * *

_Our Privacy Policy was last updated March 23, 2010_
